Guide to the Woodside-Atherton Garden Club Records SC0951
Department of Special Collections and University Archives
Woodside-Atherton Garden Club records
circa 1929-2013
Department of Special Collections and University Archives
Woodside-Atherton Garden Club
SC0951
22.75 Linear Feet (24 boxes)
The records consist primarily of meeting minutes, annual reports, news clippings, event programs, photograph albums and scrapbooks, and miscellaneous records of activities of the club from its inception forward. Photograph albums document various flower shows and local club efforts in the community.
Information about Access
Series 2: Woodside Library Garden is open for research use. Materials are otherwise restricted for 75 years from date of creation.
Biographical/Historical Sketch
The Woodside-Atherton Garden Club was formally organized in 1929, and accepted into the Garden Club of America in 1934. The club organizes civic and educational projects, and hosts and participates in local and national flower shows.
Description of the Collection
Records consist primarily of meeting minutes, annual reports, news clippings, event programs, photograph albums and scrapbooks, and miscellaneous records of activities of the club from its inception forward. Photograph albums document various flower shows and local club efforts in the community.
Acquisition Information
This collection was given to the Stanford University Archives by the Woodside-Atherton Garden Club in June 2009, 2012, 2013
Native plant gardening -- California -- Woodside; Woodside-Atherton Garden Club; Woodside-Atherton Garden Club; Garden Club of America
- Records, Series 1
  - "Complete History of the Woodside-Atherton Garden Club, 1959-1989", 1991 (Box 1, Folder 1)
  - "Continuing History of the Woodside-Atherton Garden Club, 1989-1999" (Box 1, Folder 2)
  - Woddside Atherton Garden Club Historical Summaries, 1929-2007 (Box 1, Folder 3)
  - "History of the Woodside-Atherton Garden Club, 1929-1959" (Box 1, Folder 4)
  - "Annual Meeting of the Garden Club of America, April, 1935" (Box 1, Folder 5)
  - Garden Calendar and Diary, 1937 (Box 1, Folder 6)
  - Garden Calendar and Diary, 1938 (Box 1, Folder 7)
  - Gardening Calendar, undated (Box 1, Folder 8)
  - Woodside-Atherton Garden Club publications, undated (Box 1, Folder 9)
  - Legal Documents, 1960-2007 (Box 1, Folder 10)
  - Woodside-Atherton Garden Club PowerPoint Presentation, 2008 Mar (Box 1, Folder 11)
  - Woodside-Atherton Garden Club Tea Party, DVD, 2002 (Box 1, Folder 12)
  - Christmas Holiday Luncheon-Member Interviews [DVD], 2007 (Box 1, Folder 13)
  - Woodside-Atherton Garden Club History [audiocassette], 1976 Dec 10 (Box 1, Folder 14)
  - Garden Club of America-Annual Meeting Buttons/Lanyards, 1951, 1953, 1955 (Box 1, Folder 15)
  - Newsletters, 1990s (Box 1, Folder 16)
  - Event Programs and Certificates, 1990s (Box 1, Folder 17)
  - Clippings, 1990s (Box 1, Folder 18)
  - Photographs: Ronald McDonald Immune Wing and Pumpkin Growing, 1999; Annual Meeting, 1998; Annual Meeting at Betsy Ross's, 1997 (Box 1, Folder 19)
  - Photographs: Propagation Work at Renee Moore's, 1995; Unidentified Event, 1995; Annual Meeting, 1994; Christmas, 1994; Beach House, 1994; HP Park-Daffodil Dell, 1992; Unidentified Event, undated (Box 1, Folder 20)
  - Clippings, 1980s (Box 2, Folder 1)
  - Reports and Correspondence, 1980s (Box 2, Folder 2)
  - Event Programs, 1980s (Box 2, Folder 3)
  - Photographs, 1980s (Box 2, Folder 4)
  - Clippings, 1970s (Box 2, Folder 5)
  - Reports, Publicity, and Correspondence, 1970s (Box 2, Folder 6)
  - Photographs, 1970s (Box 2, Folder 7)
  - Clippings, 1960s (Box 2, Folder 8)
  - Reports, Publicity, and Correspondence, 1960s (Box 2, Folder 9)
  - Photographs, 1960s (Box 2, Folder 10)
  - Founder's Fund Documentation from Suzanne Eyre's Files, 1957-1970 (Box 2, Folder 11)
  - Event Programs, 1930s (Box 2, Folder 12)
  - Photographs, 1930s (Box 2, Folder 13)
  - Clippings, 1930s (Box 2, Folder 14)
  - Board and Regular Minutes, 1965-1967 (Box 2, Folder 15)
  - Board and Regular Minutes, 1967-1969 (Box 2, Folder 16)
  - Board Minutes, 1971 Jun-1973 Jun (Box 2, Folder 17)
  - Regular Minutes, 1971 Jun-1973 Jun (Box 2, Folder 18)
  - Regular Minutes, 1973 Jul 1-1975 Jun 30 (Box 2, Folder 19)
  - Board Minutes, 1973 Jul 1-1975 Jun 30 (Box 2, Folder 20)
  - Regular Minutes, 1975 Jun 10-1977 Jun 21 (Box 3, Folder 1)
  - Regular Minutes, 1975 Jun-1977 Jun 20 (Box 3, Folder 2)
  - Board and Regular Minutes, 1976 (Box 3, Folder 3)
  - Regular Minutes, 1978-1979 (Box 3, Folder 4)
  - Board Minutes, 1979 Jul 23-1981 Jun 15 (Box 3, Folder 5)
  - Regular Minutes, 1979 Sep 18-1981 Jun 16 (Box 3, Folder 6)
  - Board and Regular Minutes, Treasurer's Report, 1981-1983 (Box 3, Folder 7)
  - Board and Regular Minutes, Treasurer's Report, 1983-1985 (Box 3, Folder 8)
  - Board and Regular Minutes, Treasurer's Report, 1985-1987 (Box 3, Folder 9)
  - Board and Regular Minutes, Treasurer's Report, 1987-1989 (Box 3, Folder 10)
  - Board and Regular Minutes, Treasurer's Report, 1989-1991 (Box 3, Folder 11)
  - Board and Regular Minutes, Treasurer's Report, 1991-1992 (Box 3, Folder 12)
  - Board and Regular Minutes, 1992-1993 (Box 4, Folder 1)
  - Board and Regular Minutes, 1993-1994 (Box 4, Folder 2)
  - Board and Regular Minutes, 1994-1995 (Box 4, Folder 3)
  - Board and Regular Minutes, 1995-1996 (Box 4, Folder 4)
  - Board and Regular Minutes, 1996-1997 (Box 4, Folder 5)
  - Board and Regular Minutes, 1997-1998 (Box 4, Folder 6)
  - Board and Regular Minutes, 1998-1999 (Box 4, Folder 7)
  - Board and Regular Minutes, 1999-2000 (Box 4, Folder 8)
  - Board and Regular Minutes, 2001-2003 (Box 4, Folder 9)
  - Board and Regular Minutes, 2003-2005 (Box 4, Folder 10)
  - Board and Regular Minutes, 1980-1982 (Box 4, Folder 11)
  - Board and Regular Minutes, 1973-1975 (Box 4, Folder 12-13)
  - Woodside-Atherton Garden Club Board and Regular Minutes, 1960s (Box 5, Folder 1)
  - Filoli Historic Gardens Project, 1989 (Box 5, Folder 2)
  - Environmental Volunteers, 1996 (Box 5, Folder 3)
  - Sally MacBride - Filoli, 1996 (Box 5, Folder 4)
  - Laurel School - Menlo Park, 1995 (Box 5, Folder 5)
  - Redwood High School - Roger Heathcote, 1995 (Box 5, Folder 6)
  - Star Thistle Eradication, 1993-1995 (Box 5, Folder 7)
  - Alec Donald Park-Woodside, CA, 1993-1995 (Box 5, Folder 8)
  - Adopt-A-Hiway, 1993-1994 (Box 5, Folder 9)
  - Atherton Station Planting, 1993 (Box 5, Folder 10)
  - CHC Garden Therapy, 1993 (Box 5, Folder 11)
  - Phleger Acquisition (Box 5, Folder 12)
  - Garden Club of America Endowment Fund, 1990 (Box 5, Folder 13)
  - Clipping about Filoli (Box 5, Folder 14)
  - Wildflower Project, including photographs, 1987-1988 (Box 5, Folder 15)
  - Canada Lane at Woodside Road - Landscaping, 1986 (Box 5, Folder 16)
  - Atherton Recycle Letter, 1986 (Box 5, Folder 17)
  - Holbrook-Palmer Mini-Blinds, 1986 (Box 5, Folder 18)
  - San Francisco Landscape Garden Show, 1985-1991 (Box 5, Folder 19)
  - Woodside-Atherton Garden Club Landscape Design Project - Zone XII Mini-Meeting, 1985 (Box 5, Folder 20)
  - Coyote Point Museum Project-Completed, 1983 Nov 9 (Box 5, Folder 21)
  - Holbrook-Palmer WAGC Library, 1982 (Box 5, Folder 22)
  - Woodside Independence Hall, 1980-1981 (Box 5, Folder 23)
  - Garden Calendar Project, 1973-1974 (Box 6, Folder 1)
  - Daffodil Dell, Holbrook-Palmer Park (including slides), 1972 (Box 6, Folder 2)
  - Daffodil Dell History (Box 6, Folder 3)
  - Woodside Library Gardens, 1970 (Box 6, Folder 4)
  - Portola Valley Triangle, 1969 (Box 6, Folder 5)
  - Redwoods-GCA Project, 1969 (Box 6, Folder 6)
  - Redwoods, 2001 (Box 6, Folder 7)
  - Holbrook-Palmer Park, 1958-1967 (Box 6, Folder 8)
  - Audubon Canyon Ranch, 1963 (Box 6, Folder 9-10)
  - Woodside Civic Projects, 1938-1990 (Box 6, Folder 11)
  - Flower Show, "Visions", 1992, 1997, 2002 (Box 6, Folder 12)
  - Flower Show, "Visions", 1994 (Box 6, Folder 13)
  - Flower Show, "Visions", 1999 (Box 7, Folder 1)
  - Flower Show, "Sentimental Journey", 2003 (Box 7, Folder 2)
  - Flower Show, "Out on a Limb", 1999 (Box 7, Folder 3)
  - Flower Show, "Curtain Call", 1998 (Box 7, Folder 4)
  - Flower Show, "Show and Tell", 1995 (Box 7, Folder 5)
  - Flower Show, "Early California", 1976 (Box 7, Folder 6)
  - Garden Tour, "A Walk in Country Gardens", 1973, 1983, 2005 (Box 7, Folder 7)
  - Fundraising Event, "Needlepoint Raffle", 1998 (Box 7, Folder 8)
  - Garden Tour Fundraiser, 2005 Apr (Box 7, Folder 9)
  - Fundraising - Miscellaneous, 1970s-1980s (Box 7, Folder 10)
  - Country Fair Report, 1970 Sep 26 (Box 7, Folder 11)
  - Country Fair Report, 1967 (Box 7, Folder 12)
  - Country Fair Report, 1964 (Box 7, Folder 13)
  - Medal Awards Committee, 1986-2002 (Box 7, Folder 14)
  - Presidential Reports, 1993-2005 (Box 7, Folder 15)
  - Annual Reports, 2002-2004 (Box 7, Folder 16)
  - Annual Reports, 2001-2003 (Box 7, Folder 17)
  - Annual Reports, 2000-2001 (Box 7, Folder 18)
  - Annual Reports, 1998-2000 (Box 7, Folder 19)
  - Annual Reports, 1999 (Box 7, Folder 20)
  - Annual Reports, 1997-1998 (Box 7, Folder 21)
  - Annual Reports, 1996-1997 (Box 8, Folder 1)
  - Annual Reports, 1995-1996 (Box 8, Folder 2)
  - Horticulture Committee, Annual Report by Verna Stewart, 1995 (Box 8, Folder 3)
  - Annual Reports, 1994-1995 (Box 8, Folder 4)
  - Community Interest, 1994-1995 (Box 8, Folder 5)
  - Annual Reports, 1994 (Box 8, Folder 6)
  - Annual Reports, 1993-1994 (Box 8, Folder 7)
  - Annual Reports, 1993 (Box 8, Folder 8)
  - Annual Reports, 1991-1993 (Box 8, Folder 9)
  - Annual Reports, 1992 (Box 8, Folder 10)
  - Annual Reports, 1991-1992 (Box 8, Folder 11)
  - Annual Reports, 1990-1991 (Box 8, Folder 12)
  - Annual Reports, 1989-1990 (Box 8, Folder 13)
  - President's Annual Report, 1979-1989 (Box 8, Folder 14)
  - Annual Reports, 1989 (Box 8, Folder 15)
  - GCA Annual Report, 1988-1989 (Box 8, Folder 16)
  - Annual Reports, 1988 (Box 8, Folder 17)
  - Annual Reports, 1987 (Box 8, Folder 18)
  - Annual Reports, 1986 (Box 8, Folder 19)
  - GCA Annual Meeting, 1985 (Box 9, Folder 1)
  - Annual Reports, 1985 (Box 9, Folder 2)
  - Annual Reports, 1984 (Box 9, Folder 3)
  - Annual Reports, 1983 (Box 9, Folder 4)
  - Annual Reports, 1982 (Box 9, Folder 5)
  - Annual Reports, 1981 (Box 9, Folder 6)
  - Annual Reports, 1980 (Box 9, Folder 7)
  - Annual Committee Reports, 1979 (Box 9, Folder 8)
  - Annual Committee Reports, 1978 (Box 9, Folder 9)
  - Annual Reports - Betsy Ross, 1976-1977 (Box 9, Folder 10)
  - Annual Reports, 1975 (Box 9, Folder 11)
  - Annual Reports, 1973-1974 (Box 9, Folder 12)
  - Annual Reports, 1972-1973 (Box 9, Folder 13)
  - Annual Reports, 1970-1971 (Box 9, Folder 14)
  - Annual Reports, 1968-1969 (Box 9, Folder 15)
  - Annual Reports, 1966-1967 (Box 9, Folder 16)
  - Holbrook-Palmer and Annual Reports, 1960s (Box 9, Folder 17)
  - Annual Reports, 1962-1965 (Box 9, Folder 18)
- Woodside Library Garden, Series 2
  - Pacific Horticulture, 2006 Oct-Dec (Box 10, Folder 1)
  - "Woodside Library Native Plant Garden," by M.E. Gallagher (Box 10, Folder 2)
  - "Woodside Library Native Plant Garden," by M.E. Gallagher, 1975 (Box 10, Folder 3)
  - Woodside Library Garden Landscaping Plans, 1970 (Box 10, Folder 4)
  - Woodside Library Garden - Miscellaneous (Box 10, Folder 5-6)
  - Woodside Library Garden Files, 1969-1993 (Box 10, Folder 7)
  - Woodside Library Garden - Timmy Gallagher (Box 10, Folder 8-9)
  - Woodside Library Garden - Plant List and Guide (Box 10, Folder 10)
  - Woodside Library Native Plant Garden Slides (Box 10, Folder 11)
  - Photographs, "Out on a Limb" Flower Show, 1999 (Box 10, Folder 12)
  - Program - Garden Club of America, 1985 (Box 10, Folder 13)
  - Album: Woodside Library Garden (Box 11)
  - Album: Woodside-Atherton Garden Club, 1993-1999 (Box 11)
  - Album: Woodside-Atherton Garden Club, 1999-2002 (Box 11)
  - Album: Woodside-Atherton Garden Club, 1982-1994 (Box 11)
  - Album: Suzanne Eyre's Album, 1973 (Box 12)
  - Album: "Golden Days" Flower Show and Tour of Carmel Homes, 1986; "Carousel of Flowers" Flower Show, 1989 (Box 12)
  - Album: Garden Club of America-Annual Meeting, 1985 (Box 12)
  - Small Album: Ronald McDonald House, 1993; Menlo Circus Club, 1996; Flower Arranging Workshop, 1996 (Box 12)
  - Small Album: Mini Flower Show "Show and Tell" at Regular Meeting, 1995 (Box 12)
  - Small Album: Other Club Flower Shows, 2004 (Box 12)
  - Small Album: Why Worry Farm Flower Show, 1982 (Box 12)
  - Small Album: "Visions of San Francisco", 1994 (Box 12)
  - Scrapbook: Woodside-Atherton Garden Club, 1975-1981 (Box 13)
  - Scrapbook: Woodside-Atherton Garden Club, Zone XII Meeting, 1978 (Box 13)
  - Scrapbook: Woodside-Atherton Garden Club, 1968-1975 (Box 13)
  - Scrapbook: Woodside-Atherton Garden Club, 1963-1967 (Box 13)
  - Scrapbook: Woodside-Atherton Garden Club Pictures, 1952-1962 (Box 13)
  - Album: Woodside-Atherton Garden Club, 2002-2003 (Box 14)
  - Album: Woodside-Atherton Garden Club, 2003-2004
  - Album: "Visions of San Francisco", 1994 (Box 15)
  - Album: "Sentimental Journey", 2003 (Box 15)
  - Loose Album/Scrapbook Pages (Box 16)
  - Creative Design Through Photographs (Box 17)
- Additional Records, ACCN ARCH.2012-019
  - Recording Secretary (1 of 2), 1993-1997 (Box 1, Folder 1)
  - Recording Secretary (2 of 2) (Box 1, Folder 2)
  - Minutes and Calendars (1 of 3), 1997-2003 (Box 1, Folder 3)
  - Minutes and Calendars (2 of 3), 1997-2003 (Box 1, Folder 4)
  - Minutes and Calendars (3 of 3), 1997-2003 (Box 1, Folder 5)
  - Recording Secretary, 2003-2004 (Box 1, Folder 6)
  - Woodside-Atherton Garden Club: Garden Club of America Public Relations Award, 2008 (Box 1, Folder 7)
  - Minutes of the Annual Meeting, 2010 (Box 1, Folder 8)
  - Plant Sale, 2010, 2012 (Box 1, Folder 9)
  - Stationery (Box 1, Folder 10)
  - Woodside-Atherton Garden Club: Garden Club of America Zone Conservation Award, 2006 May (Box 2, Folder 1)
  - Garden Club of America material
    - GCA: Report, 1977 (Box 1, Folder 11)
    - GCA: Fact Sheet, 1979-1980 (Box 1, Folder 12)
    - GCA: Annual Meeting, 1985 (Box 1, Folder 13)
    - GCA: Annual Meeting (photographs), 1992 (Box 1, Folder 14)
    - GCA: Annual Meeting, 1997 (Box 1, Folder 15)
    - GCA: Zone XII Biennial Meeting, 1998 (Box 1, Folder 16)
    - GCA: Annual Meeting, 1998 (Box 1, Folder 17)
    - GCA: Zone XII Presidents Council, 1999 (Box 1, Folder 18)
    - GCA: 86th Annual Meeting, 1999 (Box 1, Folder 19)
    - GCA: 87th Annual Meeting, 2000 (Box 1, Folder 20)
    - GCA: Annual Report, 2000-2001 (Box 1, Folder 21)
    - GCA: Zone XII Meeting (stationery and ephemera), 2008 (Box 1, Folder 22)
    - GCA Pub: Fifty Blooming Years, 1913-1963 (Box 1, Folder 23)
    - GCA Pub: Winds of Change 1963-1988: 75th Anniversary Chronicle (Box 1, Folder 24)
    - GCA Pub: Flower Show and Judging Guide, 1968 (Box 1, Folder 25)
    - GCA Pub: The Garden Locater of the Garden Club of America, 1953 (Box 1, Folder 26)
    - GCA Pub: Guide to Public Gardens, 1976 (Box 1, Folder 27)
    - GCA: Meeting Programs, 1946-1970 (non-inclusive) (Box 1, Folder 29)
    - GCA: Meeting Programs, 1972-1976 (non-inclusive) (Box 1, Folder 30)
    - GCA: Meeting Programs, 1977-1982 (non-inclusive) (Box 1, Folder 31)
    - GCA: Meeting Programs, 1985-2000 (non-inclusive) (Box 1, Folder 32)
  - Restricted Member Information
    - Member Addesses, 2003-2004 (Box 3)
    - Member Directories, 2012-2013 (Box 3)
- Additional Records, ACCN ARCH.2013-011
  - General/Board Meeting Minutes, 2000-2001 (Box 1, Folder 1)
  - Continuing History of Woodside-Atherton Garden Club, 2000-2010 (Box 1, Folder 2)
  - Photographs, undated (Box 1, Folder 3)
  - The Garden Club of America, Zone XII Meeting, 1978 (Box 1, Folder 4)
  - Visions of San Francisco: A Flower and Horticulture Show, 1992 (Box 1, Folder 5)
  - Visions of San Francisco: A Flower and Horticulture Show, 1994 (Box 1, Folder 6)
  - Visions Salutes the Millennium: A Major Flower Show of the Garden Club of America, 1999 (Box 1, Folder 7)
  - Visions Art! A Major Flower Show of the Garden Club of America, 2002 (Box 1, Folder 8)
  - "Down the Garden Path" (The Hillsborough Garden Club Flower Show), 1990 (Box 1, Folder 9)
  - Woodside-Atherton Garden Club: A Summer Garden Part and Auction, 1993 Jun 27 (Box 1, Folder 10)
  - "Curtain Call" Flower Show Report (1 of 2), 1998 (Box 2, Folder 1)
  - "Curtain Call" Fundraiser (1 of 2), 1998 (Box 2, Folder 3)
  - "Curtain Call" Fundraiser (2 of 2), 1998 (Box 2, Folder 4)
  - "Out on a Limb" Flower Show Report (1 of 2), 1999 (Box 2, Folder 5)
  - "Out on a Limb" Flower Show Report (2 of 2), 1999 (Box 2, Folder 6)
  - "Sentimental Journey" Flower Show Report, 2003 (Box 2, Folder 7)
  - Restricted Member Information
    - Member Directories, 2012-2013 (Box 3, Folder 1)
- Additional Records, ACCN ARCH.2013-018
  - History of the WAGC, 1929-1959 (Box 1, Folder 1)
  - Complete History of the WAGC, 1929-1989 (Box 1, Folder 2)
  - Continuing History, 1999-2009 (Box 1, Folder 3)
  - Club Historian/Working File (Box 1, Folder 4)
  - Archiving Policies/Guidelines from GCA (Box 1, Folder 5)
  - WAGC/Stanford (Box 1, Folder 6)
  - WAGC History (Box 1, Folder 7)
  - Master for 1929-1989 History (Box 1, Folder 8)
  - GCA - Redwood Tour, 1969 (Box 1, Folder 9)
  - WAGC Plant Sale Committee Report, 2010 (Box 1, Folder 10)
  - Club History Reports, 2007- (Box 1, Folder 11)
  - Policies/Bylaws (Box 1, Folder 12)
  - CIPA (Box 1, Folder 13)
  - Conservation (Box 1, Folder 14)
  - Garden Tour Report, 2005 (Box 1, Folder 15)
  - Long Range Planning (Box 1, Folder 16)
  - Medal Awards Committee (Box 1, Folder 17)
  - Nominating Committee (Box 1, Folder 18)
  - President's Report (Box 1, Folder 19)
  - Program (Box 1, Folder 20)
  - Program Hosts/Hospitality (Box 1, Folder 21)
  - Provisional Chair (Box 1, Folder 22)
  - Treasurer/Duties (Box 1, Folder 23)
  - Visiting Gardeners (Box 1, Folder 24)
  - Ways and Means (Box 1, Folder 25)
  - Woodside Library Garden (Box 1, Folder 26)
  - Various Reports, 2008-2010 (Box 1, Folder 27)
  - Horticulture Committee, 1985-2009 (Box 1, Folder 28)
  - Board Minutes/Meeting Minutes/Calendars, 2005 Sep-2006 Jun (Box 1, Folder 29)
  - Board Minutes/Meeting Minutes/Calendars, 2006 Sep-2007 Jun (Box 1, Folder 30)
  - WAGC Club History, 2000- (Box 1, Folder 31)
  - WAGC Minutes and Calendars, 2004-2007 (Box 1, Folder 32)
  - Clippings (Box 1, Folder 33)
  - Woodside Library (Box 1, Folder 34)
  - WAGC - Gardening Calendar (Box 1, Folder 35)
  - WAGC Garden Calendar and Diary, 1937 (Box 1, Folder 36)
  - Gentry Magazine article, 2005 (Box 1, Folder 37)
  - Out on a Limb program, 1999 (Box 1, Folder 38)
  - A Walk in Country Gardens program, 2005 (Box 1, Folder 39)
  - WAGC Directory, 2010-2011 (Box 1, Folder 40)
  - Portola Valley Platinum Show, 2009 (Box 1, Folder 41)
  - GCA - San Francisco, 1985 (Box 1, Folder 42)
  - Pacific Horticulture, 2006 Oct-Dec (Box 1, Folder 43)
  - GCA Bulletin, 1999 Apr (Box 1, Folder 44)
  - GCA Bulletin (various), 2008 (Box 1, Folder 45)
  - GCA Bulletin (various), 2009-2010 (Box 1, Folder 46)
  - Photographs - Decorating Committee (Box 1, Folder 47)
  - WAGC Luncheon, 2012 Jun 5 (Box 1, Folder 48)
  - Library Garden powerpoint, 2011 (Box 1, Folder 49)
  - Plant Sale photographs, 2004, 2006, 2010 (Box 1, Folder 50)
  - Restricted
    - Junior League Yearbook, 1973-1974 (Box 2, Folder 1)
    - WAGC Directory, 1996-1997 (Box 2, Folder 2)
    - WAGC Directory, 1998-1999 (Box 2, Folder 3)
    - WAGC Directory, 1999-2000 (Box 2, Folder 4)
    - WAGC Directory, 2006-2007 (Box 2, Folder 5)
    - WAGC Directory, 2007-2008 (Box 2, Folder 6)
    - WAGC Directory, 2008-2009 (Box 2, Folder 7)
    - WAGC Directory, 2009-2010 (Box 2, Folder 8)
    - WAGC Directory, 2011-2012 (Box 2, Folder 9)
- Additional Records, ACCN ARCH.2014-009
  - Yerba Buena Visions, 2000 (Box 1, Folder 1)
  - Out on a Limb (Box 1, Folder 2)
  - Visit to Annie's Annuals (Box 1, Folder 3)
  - Woodside-Atherton Garden Club Events (Box 1, Folder 4)
  - Vision Millennium, 1999 (Box 1, Folder 5)
  - Visions of San Francisco, 1997 (Box 1, Folder 6)
  - WAGC Flower Show (Box 1, Folder 7)
  - Anniversary Tea, 2002 Nov. (Box 1, Folder 8)
  - Woodside-Atherton Garden Club's "Curtain Call" Show, 25 Apr. 1998 (Box 1, Folder 9)
  - Visions of San Francisco, 1994 (Box 1, Folder 10)
  - WAGC June Lunch, 1996 (Box 1, Folder 11)
  - Flower Viewing (Box 1, Folder 12)
  - Woodside-Atherton Gardening Club Event, circa 1996 (Box 1, Folder 13)
  - Orinda Piedment, Pasadena Show (Box 1, Folder 14)
  - WAGC Album, 1990-2000 (Box 1, Folder 15)
  - Flower Arranging Workshop Demonstration - Soho Sakai @ WAGC (Box 1, Folder 16)
  - Strybing (Box 1, Folder 17)
  - Gail Emmon's Leaf Manipulation Workshop, 2001 Feb. (Box 1, Folder 17)
  - Carolyn Butcher's Potting Shed (Box 1, Folder 18)
  - Diana Schilling (Box 1, Folder 19)
  - LJ & Charlotte (Box 1, Folder 20)
  - Tina & Jessie (Box 1, Folder 21)
  - Carolyn J. & Jana (Box 1, Folder 22)
  - Lurline (Box 1, Folder 23)
  - Scrapbooks for WAGC, 1982-2004 (Box 2, Folder 1)
  - Scrapbooks for WAGC, 1930-1973 (Box 2, Folder 2)
  - Flower Show Albums for WAGC, 1982-2004 (Box 2, Folder 3)
  - Flower Shows, 1976-2002 (Box 1, Folder 27, Box 2, Folder 4)
  - Fundraisers, 1964-1998 (Box 1, Folder 28, Box 2, Folder 5)
  - Scrapbooks for WAGC, 1990-2006 (Box 2, Folder 6)